The seasonal uniform change!
It's been so muggy lately, you know?
Even just changing into short sleevesfeels much more comfortable.
Right.
RESPONSIBILITY AND DUTY
Relationship advice?
Yes! I don't know what to do.
But I heard that the student councilgives advice for that kind of thing, too.
KAGUYA WANTS TO HANDLE IT
You're the only one I can count on,Miss Kaguya!
Understood.
The president here often saysthat lending an ear to the students' troubles
is also a duty of the student council.
So,
what's the trouble?
I want to know how to break upsmoothly with my boyfriend.
I thought it would betwo or three steps before that point!
Advice about having a boyfriend.
You're really popular, and I'm sureyou know a lot about love!
But I've never even gone out with anyone,so how could I possibly answer that?
I knew I could come to youfor a great idea!
Her expectations are too high!
But Shinomiya gave romantic advice once,
so there's no wayI can tell her it's beyond me!
I'll just have to get through it somehow!
Why do you want to break up?
Actually, he suddenly asked me out.
Bam!
I said, "Okay" on the spur of the moment,
but I didn't really know him.
And I don't really knowhow to communicate with him either.
In fact, there's more distancebetween us now than before.
I feel guilty about it,
so if it's going to be like this, I figuredmaybe we're better off just breaking up.
I see.
Until just before,you were strangers to each other.
So I can see where you're coming from.
You don't hate him, though, do you?
Of course not. But I don't knowif what I feel for him is love.
Why don't you startby telling me his good points?
What I like about him?
Yes. Everyone has strong pointsor something that's cute about them.
For example, he's honestor he does well academically.
Maybe he studies hardor he's actually really kind
and can't turn his backon someone who's in trouble.
Maybe he has a menacing look.
A menacing look is a drawback.
No! Being botheredby your own menacing look is cute!
You like boys who have menacing looks?
Forget I said that.
The only person around youwith a menacing look that I can think of...
That's the wrong idea.Now let's continue.
If you find one good thing about himand start to appreciate that,
you'll soon be able to seemany of his good points,
and the next thing you know,you're unable to take your eyes off of him.
And if you see him every day...
little by little, you'll fall in love.
That's what an acquaintance told me!
I'm not talking about me!
Really?
It's really not about me!
Because there isn't anyoneI'm in love with!
But the way you said it...
I overheard!
Miss Fujiwara?
It's no fair to have girls' talk without me!
Please leave an issue like thatto Love Detective Chika!
LOVE DETECTIVE CHIKA
Why are you breathing hard?
Actually, I was here from the beginning,
but made a mad dash to the drama clubto borrow this costume.
You're in a quandary, because you can'tfind your feelings for him.
Right?
Yes.
Then this great detective will findthat lost property called "love"
and return it to you.
So, imagine him flirting with another girl.
What is this?
Just try to imagine it.
Gloomy.
GLOOMY...
Grrr.
GRRR GRRR
I didn't like that feeling.
Right?
In other words, that's jealousy.
You don't like that imagebecause you like him.
The more unpleasant the feeling,the deeper the love!
Love?
So, you also like him, Miss Kashiwagi.
No, there's no way.
I don't feel that way about the president,right? I mean, come on.
You should take that feelingand nurture it.
I see.
I suspected myself of being a cold personfor not being able to fall in love with someone
who went as far as professinghis love for me.
But...
you're right! I actually do love him!
It's like she was talked into it!
What should I doto talk to him more naturally?
I have to givemore appropriate advice, too!
Good question.
Cognitive balance.
You can probably usethe Romeo and Juliet effect.
- Romeo and Juliet?- Romeo and Juliet?
Romeo and Juliet's love faced obstacles.
The idea is that love deepens
when a couple sharesa powerful enemy they face.
A powerful enemy?
It doesn't have to be a person.
A shared imaginary enemy is fine.
We don't have an enemy like that.
Oh no! Everyone hasa powerful enemy they have to face!
Wh-Who?
It's...
this society!
Society?
Unending war! The ever-expanding gapbetween rich and poor!
There are no enemiesmore powerful than that!
Wait. It should be something minorlike entrance exams or everyday troubles.
I-I see! So the two of usshould rebel against this corrupt society!
That's a large-scale challenge!
Understood!The two of us will prepare!
Good luck!
Wait! Hold on!
Will it be okay? Did we just createtwo antisocial deviants?
It'll be fine!
Please donate to the fund!
Please!
It seems they were bothalready interested in charity work.
This has become a good opportunity.
The feeling of wishing for peace...
That may be the true meaningof rebelling against society.
What are you talking about?
So, her boyfriend is the onewho went to the president for advice.
President?
Shinomiya!
Why are you here with them?
Oh, I applied to dooff-campus fundraising activities.
Please donate to the fund!
Well, when I saw those two who don't seemto be doing it on a whim or as a pastime,
Please!
who are inexperienced but eager...
Please donate to the fund!
it made me feel like supporting themeven if it's not much.
Please!
Jeez.
Please donate to the fund!
This kind of activityreally isn't up my alley, though.
Please!
This is one of the things.
RESULTS OF TODAY'S MATCH:
Results of today's match...
KAGUYA LOSES
Kaguya loses.
PLEASE DONATE TO THE FUND
PLEASE
MIYUKI SHIROGANEWANTS TO SHOW OFF
WHACK
I was so close!
Not athletic!
NOTE: NOT ATHLETIC
When it comes to studying,Shirogane excels,
but as for athletics, he's a catastrophe,unfit for any human to see.
He delivered newspapers for many years,and in the summertime, worked as a mover.
He's easily able to ride his bikethe 15 kilometers to school every day.
Miyuki Shirogane definitely doesn't sufferfrom a lack of physical ability.
He just has an alarming lackof coordination! That's the cause!
So, in order to protecthis social status at Shuchiin Academy,
daily extraordinary training is essential!
We've got volleyball next week.
I have to get to the pointof average ability by then.
At this rate...
Please take this seriously.
It looks like a dying alpaca,but is that the president?
Really?
That dying alpaca?
How cute.
No!
Why isn't this working?
President, are you okay?
Yeah, no prob...
Fujiwara!
What are you doing?
I forgot this here. Um...
Did she see me?
It's over.Good at both sports and studies...
The well-roundedPresident Shirogane brand...
Even though I didn't do anything wrong,my flawless image will...
Did I study for the test? Not really.
This is really bad.
Playing with a ball is so much fun!
Oh, well.
Whatever she thinks about me,it won't do much damage.
Volleyball is the next sport for P.E., right?
I was able to reserve the gym,so I've been practicing.
My serve is kind of weak, you know?
Oh, I see.
Want me to teach you?
Look, you can't teach someoneunless you can do it yourself.
I'm okay at volleyball!
See?
Right?
Incredible!
PRESIDENT'S CRITERIA
How could her serve be so polished?
How'd you like that?
I-I had no idea you possessedsuch a special skill!
I bet if I taught you,you'd improve in no time.
GRIN GRIN
President! When you'reasking someone for help,
what kind of attitude is appropriate?
P-Please teach me.
Sure! No problem!
Okay, first let me seeexactly what the problem is.
Please show me your serve several times.
Okay.
Why does that happen?
I don't know myself.
No matter how many times I try,I keep hitting myself in the head.
And if I'm careful about my head,my timing is totally off.
I'm perfectly deadlocked!
Right.
First of all, when you hit the ball,keep your eyes open!
You don't have to state the obvious.
Right, right!
Then open your eyes wideand try to hit the ball.
As if that would make a difference.
See? That didn't work.
Your eyes aren't open!
They're not open!
How can you project the feeling,"I did what you said, but it didn't work"?
Look! They weren't even openone millimeter!
I don't believe it!
Maybe I have what they call "the yips"?
What arrogance!
President, maybe your image of yourselfisn't in sync with your actual movements!
Let's start with jumpingwith your eyes open!
I'm going to be merciless with you,so be prepared!
Please!
OGRE
And so...
1, 2,
3, 4 ,5...
556, 557, 558, 559...
984, 985, 986 ,987...
No closed eyes when you jump.The ball is your friend.
And so, with morning and eveningtraining sessions, three days passed.
President...
Maybe this is enough.
I think you're good enough to beat the level of a person who just sucks at it.
Compared to when you were a creature,you've made a lot of progress.
Not yet!
I can still...
do more!
Why are you working so hard for this?
Because I don't want themto see me look like a dork.
If they're going to see me,I want them to see me look cool!
Are you talkingabout the person you like, President?
Not at all!You've got romance on the brain!
You don't have to hide it from me!
Who's she? Who's she?
Shut up!
Please tell me!
Don't pester me about that!
Y-You did it!
You did it! You did it!
Yeah, Fujiwara. Thanks to you.
It was so tough!But you persevered until you achieved it!
All right, Fujiwara.
Next teach me how to toss and receive!
ONE WEEK LATER
Wow!
Shirogane!
Miss Fujiwara?
I raised that boy.
You're his mother?
RESULTS OF TODAY'S MATCH:
Results of today's match...
Shirogane and Fujiwara's victory!
SHIROGANE ANDFUJIWARA'S VICTORY
YES, WELL...
I'LL NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
KAGUYA WANTS TO BE COVERED
All right. Ishigami finished dealingwith the aftermath of that last mixer...
so there really isn't anythingfor us to do today.
Shall we take the day off?
Sure! Then you'd better callfor an early pickup, Miss Kaguya.
Actually...
the car has a flat or something,so I thought I'd walk home.
You won't be kidnapped?
Not much evidence is left on a rainy day,so that's when they target you!
Please don't say thingsthat'll make me nervous.
I'd like to give you a lift,but I have somewhere to go.
Shinomiya is going to walk home?
That's okay.I appreciate the sentiment.
Then maybe that'll work?
The turning point of the season.The rainy season.
Sharing an umbrella!
Two shoulders close togetherunder one umbrella,
an event that immediately closesthe distance between man and woman.
The rainy season is the ideal seasonto share an umbrella.
What nonsense.
Shamefully jostling each otherunder one umbrella...
But I do recognize the meaningbehind sharing an umbrella.
In the realm of romance,what should be feared the most
is summer vacation magic.
"Spending summer vacationwith your sweetheart."
That brand is so sought after
that before summer vacation starts,evaluation of the opposite sex
takes place everywherethroughout the school.
Sharing an umbrella emphasizes to onlookersan intimacy with a member of the opposite sex,
DAMN
MARKING COMPLETE!!
HE'S TAKEN
and is the most efficient wayto mark someone as being excluded
from the groupof "summer sweetheart candidates."
It's really coming down.
Yes. It wasn't raining at all this morning.
There's pretty much one waythat sharing an umbrella works.
One... "A" has forgotten to bringan umbrella and is just standing there.
Two... Unable to ignore that,"B" asks, "Wanna share?"
WANNA SHARE?
SUCCESS!!
Well, should we go?
In short, the successof sharing an umbrella...
Yes.
depends on the "I forgot my umbrella" appeal!
However...
What should I do?I don't have an umbrella.
Shoot, I forgot my umbrella.
COMPETITION BATTING!!
Batting!
An umbrella sharing event beginswith one person forgetting their umbrella.
But if they both forget their umbrellas,there are no developments!
It's just two peoplewho have forgotten to bring an umbrella!
Y-You forgot your umbrella, too, Shinomiya?
Yes. It just slipped my mind,since I usually get picked up.
Why did you forget?
Well, I didn't check the weather forecast.
I didn't thinkwe were in for a storm like this.
Of course, it's all a bluff!
They both have folding umbrellasin their bags!
What do I do?Tell her I have an umbrella now?
But if I do that...
Oh, my.
You wanted to get under my umbrellaso badly that you lied about your umbrella?
Good grief.
How cute.
I can't!
Already, taking out the umbrellawould expose a meaningful lie.
And that would also directly link to invitingthe other person to share the umbrella.
That would clearly spell defeat.
Wait. If she doesn't have a ride,
I'm sure someone from the Shinomiya housewould've given her an umbrella.
It wouldn't matterthat it slipped her mind!
I've got your number, President.
You have an umbrellain that bag, don't you?
You're lying because you're too embarrassedto invite me under your umbrella.
In this situation,the condition for victory...
is none other than exposingthe other person's lie!
Hey, Shinomiya,maybe you've actually got one.
Shirogane made the first move.
Your usual ride had a flat today,on the day it rains.
But today of all days, someone like you,who always plans ahead, forgot her umbrella.
How likely is that?
What are you trying to say?
Oh, nothing.
Not enough information.
Should I gamble on a game-winning hit?
If we're talking planning ahead,you do the same, President.
What?
Before, you said you didn't checkthe weather forecast, but I find that odd.
What's odd about it?
I have days like that.
You always ride your bicycleto school, don't you?
Yes, but...
Then,
why did you take the train today?
I noticed your bikewasn't in the bike rack today.
What?
I mean, if you think about it,there's nothing unnatural at all.
On a rainy day,you take the train to school.
That's the reasonable thing to do, isn't it?
Say, President...
you said you missedthe weather forecast, right?
Then why did you chooseto take the train today, of all days?
The truth is...
you saw it, didn't you?
The weather forecast.
The difference in preparation!
Maybe you just thoughtyou forgot to bring an umbrella.
President, would you take a lookin your bag to see if it's there?
The difference in advance preparationwill decide the outcome of the game!
It didn't even take Shirogane an hourto devise his umbrella-sharing plan.
On the other hand,Kaguya confirmed the weather report.
She carefully looked at the weather map,
used an awl to piercethe tire of her ride,
and checked the bicycle rack.
The amount of advance preparationgave her a big lead.
Naturally, she predictedthis situation, as well.
Now I'll score a point for good measure!
I guess I'll just get soakedwalking home in the rain.
GRIN
Miss Kaguya, you forgot your umbrella?
I've got a spare in the classroom,so please use this one.
Please be more careful for next time!
Absent-minded Miss Kaguya!
Well, see ya tomorrow!
I had him! I was one step away!
Why does that girl always spoil it?
Now that it's come to this...
Here.
I'm giving you this umbrella, President!
Do what you want with it! Here!
No, that umbrella belongs to Fujiwara.
I'm subletting it!
No, look...
All right.
How about I borrow half of it?
I suppose that will do.
Results of today's match...
RESULTS OF TODAY'S MATCH:
A tie.
A TIE