The Rising of the Shield Hero
The Savior of the Heavenly Fowl
I've received an order for herbicide, Shield Hero.
A village to the south needs a lot of it, and immediately.
You're the only one I can ask. You have the Heavenly Fowl.
Why would they need herbicide so quickly, and so much of it?
Master, the plants here are amazing.
Yeah, you'd definitely need herbicide for this.
Look, Naofumi-sama.
Take us there, Filo.
Okay!
Thank you so much.
This place was about to fall to the vines, too.
Couldn't you have burned them?
We tried everything we could think of.
We even summoned adventurers,but the situation remains grave.
Our village was already overrun by vines.
What's worse, the plants turned into monsters and attacked us.
Turned into monsters?
Some adventurers set out for the village to level up.
I tried to stop them, but to no avail.
Filo, grab the adventurers and bring them back here.
Okay. Be wighd bag.
Plant monsters were all over the place.
Some even spat poison or acid.
Why would these guys go there when they're so weak?
They must be stupid.
You didn't have to say that last part.
Huh?
Don't "huh" me.
Ugh...
Hey, that bird that talked.
Don't "ugh" me either.
Tch.
Could it be...
That has to be the Heavenly Fowl!
The Savior of the Heavenly Fowl has come to our village, too!
Are you the savior who travels in a carriage drawn by a heavenly fowl?
You've got the wrong guy.
Naofumi-sama...
We beg you!
Could you please heal our sick using your powers?
Wait, some of you are sick?
As you can see, the plants are devouring their bodies.
They're even parasitic?
Please, Savior! Help them with your powers!
I can't say for sure that I'll be able to heal them.
Potion Enhance
Next.
Yeah.
I'm glad it went well.
But we're leaving as soon as we get paid for the treatment.
I don't want to be dragged any further into this mess.
I daresay that might be difficult.
Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl!
Please save our village!
Our village was being ravaged by famine when the Spear Hero visited.
When he heard of our plight,
he went to some nearby ruins and brought back a seed that had been sealed there.
He called it a miracle seed.
A miracle seed that was sealed away?
That was it, huh?
At first, we were overjoyed when we saw how quickly the plants grew and bore fruit.
However...
They grew too much and overwhelmed your village?
Indeed.
While investigating our options,
we hit upon a legend passed down the village.
A long time ago, an alchemist who'd set up shop in this area created a seed,
but sealed it away for some reason.
The legend also said that plants had overtaken the region for a while.
Hold on a second.
Why did none of you have doubts about that seed if you knew about this legend?
You convinced yourself it was safe because a hero brought it to you?
We'll pay for treatments, and for the monster extermination, in advance!
Please save our village!
I don't like cleaning up after that moron Motoyasu,
but I'll earn my keep.
That shield... Could it be?
Let's go, Filo!
Take that thing out, and it'll all be over?
I hope it's that easy.
Master, I'm going.
Wait, Filo!
Air Strike Shield!
It regenerates too quickly.
If normal attacks won't work...
Raphtalia...
Splash this herbicide directly on that eyeball.
Got it!
Let's go, Filo.
Okay.
Don't hold me back, Onee-chan!
H-Hold you back?
Watch out!
Did you just laugh, Filo?
No, I did not.
Never mind that. Get the herbicide.
"Never mind"?
Regenerating again?
Come to think of it...
If the Potion Enhance skill works on the herbicide as well...
Stay away, Naofumi-sama!
You're amazing, Master!
This is what the Shield Hero can do...
Potion Enhance
It's working!
Get back, you two!
Those seeds could cause more trouble.
Let's gather them up.
That one was mine.
I got it first.
Me!
No, me!
What am I gonna do with them?
Bio Plant Shield
Plant Modification?
What are you doing?
I unlocked a skill called Plant Modification, so I tried a little experiment.
We just barely took down that monster, so please don't be so reckless.
Thank you so much, Our Savior... No, Shield Hero!
I exterminated the monsters.
You guys clean up the withered vines yourselves.
R-Right...
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
Oh, sure.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's hard to get a read on the Shield Hero, isn't it?
Yes.
He's so quiet and cool, isn't he?
U-Uh... right.
Plant Analysis Skill Unlocked
Bio Plant Seed
I guess that'll do it.
Naofumi-sama?
You can sleep some more.
No, it's fine.
Is that a seed from yesterday?
Wait and watch.
Like I said, please don't take such risks...
It worked.
Those look yummy!
I curbed their breeding and mutation potential,
then increased their growth and productivity.
With this, they should bear lots of edible fruit without turning into monsters.
Wow.
The village will never have to worry about famine again.
Thank you so much, Sir Hero!
Not only did you save us from danger,
you're giving us such a wonderful gift!
Who said anything about giving it to you?
Let's cut a deal.
I'll sell you these seeds.
For the right price, of course.
You're too greedy, Naofumi-sama.
B-But we paid everything we had for the treatment and extermination.
You can also exchange goods for them.
What? But we have nothing left...
This is fun!
Those guys are really tough-minded.
This feels great!
We have so much fruit,
most of it will rot before we can eat it.
Don't worry. I know someone we can sell it to.
This seed certainly is very impressive.
I'll gladly buy it all, including the produce.
We have a deal, then.
You placed several attractive products in sight to create an advantage.
You truly are a shining example of the trader's spirit!
Is that so?
Oh, yes.
If you aren't busy, could I request your assistance with a job?
There's a hot springs town not too far away from here.
I need you to deliver some goods to an inn there.
Great. The order is complete.
See you.
There are hot springs towns in this world, too?
So warm!
Hey, Master.
I wanna go in this hot spring thing, too.
Hot spring, huh?
How about you, Raphtalia?
I'm not that interested.
But if you and Filo want to go, I'll accompany you.
That's that. We're spending the night here.
Thank you—
Master!
I wuv you!
I'm happy that we're staying in a hot springs inn,
but Filo's being too clingy with Naofumi-sama.
I want to be clingy with him, too!
"The origin of this hot spring, and its benefits"?
What does a silver boar have to do with a hot spring?
Whatever.
Its effects are... success in love?!
"A couple that enters this hot spring together will be united forever"?!
Th-Then, if I can take a b-bath together with Naofumi-sama...
N-No, Naofumi-sama!
We can't k-k-kiss! I'll get pregnant!
Wow, an open-air bath?
Naofumi-sama?
So big!
Filo, don't swim in the bath.
I can't?
Wait, is that okay in this world?
I was wondering why Filo wasn't here yet,and she's with Naofumi-sama?
You swim too, Master.
I'm not going to.
Then wash my hair.
Can't you do it yourself?
In the end, Filo was with Naofumi-sama the whole time.
Anyway, I want to share this drink with him.
That feels good, Master.
You have way too much hair. Brushing it is a pain.
Really?
Raphtalia had much shorter hair.
I wish he'd brush my hair too, like before.
Um...
I also...
Master, I'm thirsty.
Sit still,
or I won't brush your hair again.
No! It feels good, so keep going!
Also, do my feathers, too.
Do your wings yourself.
What's up, Raphtalia?
Nothing.
Onee-chan, gimme.
I have to do something, or Filo will steal my Naofumi-sama.
If I want to turn this around all at once...
Mom used to say that a gift was the best way to get your beloved's attention.
She fell in love with Dad after he gave her a gift, too.
If I can give him some latium...
Hey, have you heard of latium?
Oh, you mean that rare crystal found in this area?
Apparently, love charms made with it work really well.
What? Really?
A bird called a gagocco collects latium,
so if I find one of their nests,I'll get my hands on some!
And then, I'll give it to Naofumi-sama...
W-We mustn't, Naofumi-sama!
Like I said, if we kiss...
What's this about Master?
Huh? That voice...
Filo?
Why is she up in the mountains?
Is she after the latium, too?
You're here for the eggs too, aren't you?
Huh?
The old man at the inn told me
that the eggs of a bird called a gagocco are a rare delicacy.
Oh, she's just being a glutton like always.
She's still such a child.
If I take a rare delicacy to Master,
I'm sure he'll pet me and become my mate.
M-Mate?!
Mating means marriage!
Filo's thinking that far ahead?
So I won't let you have the eggs, Onee-chan.
Wait up!
Eggs, eggs, yummy eggs!
When did this become a race?
You're so slow, Onee-chan.
Watch out, Filo!
Ow...
Are you okay, Onee-chan?
Yeah. Are you okay?
Yep. Thanks.
It's good that this thing cushioned our fall.
What now?!
Onee-chan, get on me!
That was scary.
Thank you, Filo.
Now we're even, right?
Yep!
So that's a gagocco and its nest.
Eggs, eggs!
Sorry to scare you.
I just really need that crystal.
My eggs...
Onee-chan...
Yes.
In the end, we didn't find any other gagocco nests.
Will giving Naofumi-sama this thing instead make him happy?
Hey, you guys.
Is that a silver razorback?
Huh?
Like that thing over there.
Oh.
Could you give it to us?
Silver razorbacks are valuable prey, used as offerings in town rituals.
Please! We'll pay good money for it!
Money?
Onee-chan...
For me?
Yep.
Filo and I picked it out.
We thought you might want a tool to help you craft metals.
I do...
But wasn't this pretty expensive?
It's a token of our gratitude to you, for always taking such good care of us.
Yep. A gift for you, Master.
Thanks. I'll make good use of it.
Also...
Both of you, go take a dip in the hot spring.
He still treats me like a child at times,
but I'll make him recognize my womanly charms one day!
Right, Filo?
Yep!
Godspeed.
An epidemic to the east?
Yeah. Medicine's flying off the shelves, apparently.
Where shall we head next, Naofumi-sama?
East.
Curse Shield