You fall in love with someone...
FATE
confess that love...
DESTINY
and become a couple.
Everyone would say that's a wonderful thing.
But they're wrong!
Love is war!
CONFESSION
The person who falls in love loses!
KAGUYA-SAMA: LOVE IS WAR
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Oh.
TEENS LOVE BIBLE
What's this?
Oh, the headmaster confiscated itfrom a student.
MIYUKI SHIROGANESTILL HASN'T DONE IT
He said, "It's not proper reading material,so dispose of it."
Jeez. Why didn't he just do it himself?
Not proper reading material?
CRUDE
Crude!
I mean lewd!
LEWD
This country is becoming lewd!
What's got her skirt in a bunch?
Maybe nudity with pubic hair?
Shirogane showed great interest.
- Kaguya, I wouldn't if I were you!- Let's see.
A survey. "When was your 'first time?'"
"By high school. 34%."
No way! There's no waythat many are doing it!
34%!
In other words, more than a third!
One out of three peoplemeans there's a high likelihood
DID IT
that one of these threehave already had such an experience!
I-It's only that highbecause the respondents
are the people who readthis kind of magazine, right?
Oh, you mean "sample selection bias."
Yes, there can't actually bethat many people.
Right?
Really?
This percentage seems about right to me.
In fact, it's probably low.
Um, I don't even think I need to ask,
but have you hadthat kind of experience, Kaguya?
Yes, the first was a long time ago.
TOWN PAGES
Huh. The area code for Aomori is 017.That's surprising.
Isn't that normalfor most high school students?
You two must not have been raisedin a loving environment.
M-Maybe I should hurry upand get a boyfriend.
The area code for Oshamanbein Hokkaido is 01377... and 013...
But I'm sure Father would never allow it.
Kaguya realizes there's a nervouscomponent to their reactions.
When humans realizethey've gotten a late start
compared to those around them,they get nervous.
Then that anxiety makes themsuccumb to the emotional need
of finding a romantic partner. In short...
I'm too late to the party?
I’M FALLING BEHIND?
I HAVE TO GET A GIRLFRIEND!
SHINOMIYA, GO OUT WITH ME!
Shinomiya, go out with me!
Confess your love!
Kaguya's objective of the day was decided.
The whole thing is ridiculous!
Oh, President,I heard you were very popular.
She instigates.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
She instigates some more!
No, I don't.
I don't have that kind of relationshipwith a particular person. Not right now.
"Not right now"!
An expression that hintsat the existence of a girlfriend long ago,
but even if he's never gone outwith anyone, it isn't a lie!
It's an expression loved by peoplethe world over, from the young to the elderly!
That's right! Miyuki Shiroganehas never had a romantic experience!
And yet it can't be saidthat he isn't popular.
In fact, he is quite popular.
Perhaps it should be saidbirds of a feather flock together.
Or perhaps we should consider thatin many cases, oddballs are drawn to oddballs.
When the trend is only dangerouscharacters being attracted to you,
WHAT IS THIS HAIR?
you won't reach a romantic relationship.
WHAT IS THIS SMOKE?
Why am I so popular?
And so, despite having no experience,
Shirogane was supremely confidentin his own popularity.
The women must be attractedto my overflowing intelligence.
Should I feel guilty?
Yes, this man possessesboth boundless confidence and pure chastity,
Not right now.
a combination that has made him...
...a twisted monster virgin!
Oh. Then of course you've done it, right?
But even that monster has a weakness.
MONSTER VIRGIN
He is still a virgin.
It would be easy to lie.
But telling an experienced personthat I have experience
would be like a movie neophyte claimingknowledge about movies to a film buff,
thinking they can trick the person!
Supposing I did lie to her...
I have tons of experience!
You're bragging about it?
Are you that embarrassedabout having your virginity exposed?
How cute.
She'd see through me!
I-If you're that curious,you can always ask me directly.
The best he can do is bluff.
Really?
I know you have a little sister, President,
so you probablydo it with her all the time.
Oh, that...
Of course not! Are you a moron?
Well, you're family.
I did it to my newborn nephew.
It was videotaped.
You're a loon!
Good times.
It's not good to be excessively afraidof physical contact with other people.
I guess that's the dark sideof modern society.
No, it's you!
You're the dark side of the nobility!
What's so strange?
You must do it a lot to your dog Pesu,don't you, Chika?
- You do?- No! Please don't drag me into this!
The Shinomiya family upbringingis this perverse?
She's so ignorant of the ways of the worldthat she thinks it's common sense?
Shinomiya...
Let me ask you this.
Do you know what it meansby "first time"?
Please don't make light of me.
As a lady, I know that much.
It's referring to kissing.
Honestly.
Kaguya Shinomiya.
As the daughterof the owner of a conglomerate,
she's been protectedfrom sexual information for 16 years now.
The beginning and endof her sexual education was kissing.
ALL ABOUT SEXPISTIL STAMENWHEN YOU GET MARRIED,LEAVE IT TO THE MAN.THE END
Anything more than thatshe picked up from urban legends.
So the storkhas nothing to do with it, right?
She's a "daughter in a box"taken to the extreme!
Naturally, she has no ideawhat "your first time" refers to.
Shinomiya...
President, I'll take this one.
Kaguya...
In this case, "first time" means...
And then...
puts...
in...
After that...
the two...
moving...
like beasts!
MINUTES
LATER
A-After all...
the law is you do that kind of thingafter you get married!
I thought my heart was gonna stop!
RESULTS OFTODAY'S MATCH:
SHINOMIYA LOSES
Today's match...
FOR INCREDIBLE IGNORANCEABOUT SEXUAL KNOWLEDGE
Shinomiya loses.
President, I disapproveof illicit intercourse.
So would you go do it to yourself?
KAGUYA WANTSTO BE FIGURED OUT
It's a quiet night, isn't it?
Yes.
It's Fujiwara's turn to walk Pesu today,so she had to go home early.
Pesu! Pesu!
And Ishigami was in and out of herebefore I even noticed.
He gets the perfect attendance awardin his own way.
You've mellowed outsince we first started here, Shinomiya.
You mean I've gained weight?
No, "mellow," not "marshmallow."Your personality.
Like making small talk.
Yes.
I've been making an effortto become slightly more likeable.
That's what it is?
Well, it also helps that I have a betterunderstanding of you as a person.
You understand me?
Really?
We've been working together hereat student council for half a year now.
I think I havea pretty good understanding of you.
Then I'll test you.
Test?
Yes, let's test how muchyou really know about me.
Do you know the game "20 Questions"?
20 Questions!
EXAMPLE
It's a game in which one playergets 20 questions
Is it smaller than my palm?
to guess what the other playeris thinking of.
Is it edible?
But the player can only ask questionsthat can be answered with a yes or no.
I'm thinking of an eraser.
If the guesser gets it correctlywithin 20 questions, they win.
If they can't, the other person wins.
But if you get 20 questions,you can pretty much guess it.
If you really know me, though...
you should be able to guess itwith half that, ten questions.
I see.
That's fine.
Are you ready?
Yes.
20 CHAMBER BELGIAN REVOLVER"HENRION, DASSY, AND HEUSCHEN"(BUT ONLY 10 BULLETS LOADED)
Then my first question...
One, is it something that can be touched?
Yes.
It isn't a word or concept.
- Two, is it an electrical appliance?- No.
- Three, is it something that's warm or cold?- Yes.
Considering her answers,it could be a living thing,
WARM-BLOODEDANIMAL
FOOD
food, a substancelike warm water or ice,
BOILING WATER
ICE
a bonfire or some kindof temperature control device?
FIRE...
ETC., ETC...
But since this is a testof how well I understand Shinomiya,
the answer must be somethingconnected to Kaguya Shinomiya.
Therefore...
Four, is it something you own?
No.
Five, is it something you touched today?
Six, is it something that's at your house?
No.
Three noes in a row.
I thought it was something Shinomiyapossessed, but now I don't know.
I'll explore Shinomiya's psychologya little more.
All right.
Seven, is it something you like?
Yes.
What is that expression?
She looks kind of embarrassed or bashful.
Don't tell me.
Eight...
Is it a living thing?
Yes.
It's...
It's me, isn't it?
Calm down! Let's confirm it!
You can touch it.
It isn't an electrical appliance.
It isn't room temperature.
Shinomiya doesn't own it.
She hasn't touched it,and of course, it isn't in her house.
It all matches!
And it's something that Shinomiya likes!
Is this...
a roundabout confession of love?
Nine, in what way do you like it?
THUMP THUMP
As a friend? As a human being?
Or something else?
No answer.
I can only answer with a yes or no.
Crap!
I'm so flustered, I wasted a shot!
I've got to calm down.
It's possiblethat the answer is someone else!
Okay.
Ten, is it somethingthat's very intelligent, handsome,
with somewhat light-colored hairand well-defined eyes?
It's me!
It's definitely me!
Jeez, Shinomiya...
What a twisted way to confess your love.
We've been through a lot together, huh?
That's right.
Every time, I understood moreabout the person named Shinomiya.
And...
Huh?
Well, you're out of questions.
Give me your answer.
That's right.
To a certain extent, I understandwhat kind of person Shinomiya is.
At a time like this, she always...
My answer is...
a dog.
Correct.
PESU (DOG)
More precisely,Fujiwara's dog, Pesu.
Good boy! Good boy!You're so cute!
INTELLIGENT
HANDSOME
HANDSOMELIGHT-COLORED HAIR
So shall wego home?
HANDSOMELIGHT-COLORED HAIRWELL-DEFINED EYES
It's getting late, after all.
Right.
The results of today's test...
PASS
BECAUSE WHEN ALL WAS SAID AND DONE,SHIROGANE UNDERSTOOD SHINOMIYA'S NATURE.
Pass.
I FEEL LIKE PESU REMINDS MEOF SOMEONE...
PANT PANT
Kaguya Shinomiya is the daughterof the Shinomiya family,
which was part of oneof the old financial combines.
KAGUYA WANTS TO WALK
Her life was decided when she was bornor perhaps even before she was born.
For example, this...
2,574 times.
That's the number of times
Kaguya Shinomiya has gazedout the window on the way to school.
SHINOMIYA
But one day...
A cat?
Yes.
It's lodged itself in there deepnear the engine.
I'll arrange for another car,so if you would wait for a short while...
In that case, I'll just walk there.
At least go with Hayasaka.
I don't mind.
If she waits for me to change clothes,she'll be late,
and I think she'll be finegoing on her own.
There. You see? I'll be fine.
Miss Kaguya!
See you later.
She was slightly out of breathas she ran under the refreshing sun.
All right.
I may never get the chanceto walk to school again.
I have to take advantageof this precious opportunity.
So...
I believe the presidentrides his bike to school from Setagaya,
BICYCLE LANE
so he probably takes Meiji Street.
MEIJI STREET
The president always gets to schoolon the late side,
so if I wait on the bridge, I'm sure...
Well, if I don't hurry,I'll miss the president.
What's wrong?
If you've got a problem,briefly tell me what it is.
The pedestrian crossing!
The pedestrian crossing?
All right, I'll cross with you.
Okay. Would you let go of me now?
There are a lot of pedestrian crossingson the way to school!
Before today,
how did you go to school?
With a friend.
Yeti always held my handwhen we crossed.
The Abominable Snowman?
Her name is Ienaga,so her nickname is Yeti.
But now that we're in the upper grades,
she said there's no moregroup walking to school.
So now, I'm on my own.
WAAAH WAAAH
Her thinking is still totally lower grade.
I had a better head on my shoulderseven when I was in the lower grades.
I don't want to be alone!
I want to be with everyone else!
Listen.
Just because going to school in a groupis officially over,
that doesn't meanyou have to walk to school by yourself.
You should meet up somewherewith your friend
or pick her up at her houseand walk together.
Right?
You're smart! Are you a genius?
What can I say?
Mikiti!
Yeti!
Well, you're fine now, right?
Go on.
Right!
Bye-bye, genius girl!
Good morning! Surprised to see me?
Good morning! You did surprise me!
- Let's go to school together!- Yeah!
Well, where am I?
Eight twenty-five.
I'm going to be late.
If they find out I was late,
I'll never be allowedto go to school on my own again.
I wanted to try doing it even just once.
Going to school with someone...
President?
Shinomiya?
What are you doing here?
The bell's gonna ring!
You, too. President, are you going to be—
I'm not late yet!
I've never been late yet!
You're the problem, Shinomiya!
If you walk, you'll definitely be late!
If a member of the ShuchiinStudent Council is late,
it sets a bad example!
Hop on the back!
We've gotta fly!
Being late is bad,but two people on a bike is okay?
Be quiet!When it comes to student council,
school rules take priorityover traffic rules!
Days later...
Kaguya has returned to her usual routineof going to school by car.
- Can I go to your house, Yeti?- Sure! Come over!
But sometimes...
she remembers that one day and smiles.
Go back to the forest.