Hyakkimaru got injured due to the sudden return of his hearing.
A girl named Mio took him in.
Mio lived with children who had been orphaned in the war.
But on the night Hyakkimaru went out to fight a demon...
I can't... I can't believe it.
Huh, what's that?
Bro?
What happened?
Perfect, help me out here.
Are you okay?
His leg!
He shouldn't have fought with that injury. The demon got it.
Does it hurt?
Huh? That voice...
Yes, he lost his leg but got his voice back.
Hyakkimaru's voice...?
Party is over
But I still wanna dance
I can't even sleep
Someday, one day my passion's fire will
From the beginning I knew
One day the flames would die out
Hey, I thought I didn't need anything
But even now, I'm so serious
Ah... I still have time to make it
Ah... but I'm gonna burn it up, baby
Sorry darling, it's not that easy
But surely it's not that bad either
Give me fire
Light it up, baby. I'm gonna burn it up, yeah
Party is over
Sorry darling Hurry up Ah... I still have time to make it
Give me fire
Light it up, baby. I'm gonna burn it up, yeah
#6 The story of the Moriko Song, part 2
Mio!
You're home.
Hi there.
Ow...
What did you do? You're hurt.
It's nothing, I just tripped.
Are you okay? You need to rest up.
I told you that you shouldn't work at both camps.
Stop going...
What's that?
Oh. Well, you see...
Hyakkimaru!
What happened?
It won't kill him.
It was just too early for him to fight.
Mio, never mind him. Get some sleep.
It's okay, I'm used to this.
You get food ready for everyone.
Dammit!
What, shouldn't you be keeping watch over your guy?
Yeah...
But Mio will take good care of him.
Jeez, Mio sure likes to take care of people.
After working all night.
Take, have you ever seen your sis at work?
I always stay home.
Can't leave the little ones alone.
Right.
I mean, we have to rely on her or we'll all starve to death.
I'm not blaming you or anything.
We all made a promise together to someday own our own rice paddy.
Rice paddy?
It's gonna be all green in the summer and golden in the fall.
Golden, you know?
We'll grow more rice than we can eat.
We've only seen rice paddies burnt by war or dried up by droughts.
But Mio said they all used to be golden.
Let's make our very own rice paddy some day.
Green and golden. And all ours.
I'll be able to work too in a little bit, so Mio won't have to work so hard.
Hey, Take.
Coming.
Don't worry.
War took a lot from us, so let's get it back.
We need a good rain.
Don't worry. We're blessed by rains every year.
See? There are clouds coming up.
Please, Father.
Let me join the army to suppress the Sakai clan.
I'll crush that little domain like it's nothing.
Never underestimate wars.
If that's how you think, it's too early for you. Back to your training.
-Father! -Tahomaru.
Mother.
Mother, please tell Father to let me go to war.
Your father just said no.
Then no it is, no matter what I say.
Father doesn't understand!
If only he'd let me go,
I know I'd distinguish myself in battle and make you proud.
Of all things...
My feats wouldn't impress you?
That's not what I mean.
No, you are always like that, Mother.
No matter what prize I hunt down or how great I am at martial arts,
you never care.
I just...
I do not like things to do with war.
It is not war you do not like, but me.
How can you say that?
Tahomaru, what mother would not love her child?
Hyogo, Mutsu. I wish to go riding. Bring the horses.
Young Master!
You don't have to say it. I was being a bit childish.
A bit?
Her lady is kind. Especially to you, always.
I heard you already!
Mother has never been unkind to me. Yet...
Young Master, please, that is dangerous!
You shall get hurt!
Hyogo, Mutsu, help him down!
Mother, look at me!
-Please, Young Master! -Do come down!
Young Master!
Please, you mustn't be up there!
Do you hear me?
There is something else that Mother cares for much more in this world.
She will never say it, but she is hiding something.
Not just Mother. It's the same for Father, too.
You, I, this domain. We all sit atop a small cornerstone.
Please do not forget that.
What can they be hiding?
Hyakkimaru!
You must stay put.
You mustn't go. I understand that you're frustrated, but what if you die?
I pushed myself too hard as well, so I get it.
I'm so stupid.
I knew it wasn't easy to make money.
No, no.
I'd already promised I'd never cry because of a samurai ever again.
You too. If you try too hard and die, you lose.
Anyways, I heard you found your voice.
That's amazing. Try to say something.
Is your voice too loud for you?
Really.
You'll get used to it.
Dororo said you were like a beast in a cave the way you are now.
How about a song? You like songs, right?
Pick a red flower
I sing whenever I feel sad.
Instead of crying.
Pick a red flower
To give to her
In her hair
I will put the flower
You're leaving?
Yes, just like that girl says, I'll take it slowly.
I'll just go around the place the monster is. I'm in no hurry anyway.
Although it'd be useless to try and tell Hyakkimaru that.
Why's that?
If you take a toy from a baby, it'll get mad and take it back.
Same as that.
Especially since what they took from him is his own body.
He's calm when he's listening to that song.
What do you mean?
The demon flames Hyakkimaru has had since he was a baby.
You could say they're the embers left from when they took his body.
You better hope the beast that comes out of the cave isn't a monster.
Bye now.
...white flower
Don't look at me so much.
You can see people's souls, right? The colors of them.
Please don't look at mine.
It's probably filthy. Really filthy.
How strange. I don't loathe these hands.
Lord Daigo is angry.
So no provisions?
He'll send them. Reinforcements, too.
But it would be an embarrassment to wait.
We will plan a surprise attack. Don't let them sense it.
Tell everyone to be on the watch for Sakai spies.
Yes, sir!
Going to work?
Oh, you know what my job is...
I didn't look on purpose!
It's okay, I'm not ashamed about it.
It's to survive.
But I understand if you want to keep your distance.
It's not a nice job.
But I'm amazed at how a boy your age understood what my job was.
I traveled around with my mama a lot.
And that's the only job Mama didn't do no matter how hungry we got.
What an admirable mama.
But Mama...
That's how she died...
Mama was admirable, but so are you for staying alive.
You are, darn it!
You're gonna take back what war took from you, right?
Then take it all! Rice paddies, farms, everything!
I will. Thanks.
Here, eat up.
Come on, it'll make you stronger.
So what if you lost a leg?
You got your voice back, so say something.
Come on, you need to eat if you want to use that voice.
Here, have some water.
Sorry.
Hey, Hyakkimaru?
You won't lose to it, will you?
You'll never become a monster, right?
Anyways, eat up now.
Pick a red flower
To give to her
In her...
Oh, wow!
That's so cool.
I'm going to work, but don't let Hyakkimaru go to fight it.
His body isn't ready for it.
I know.
That's so cool. It's stuck on your arm?
But we've got something cool, too.
We found them at the battlefield.
Look, pretty nice, huh?
Mama...
Hyakkimaru!
Seems like the rain's coming. Finally!
Mio, we're in trouble!
Hyakkimaru went to beat the monster!
Dororo went after him!
Hyakkimaru!
That's it? Give me a break!
Jeez, how could you go without telling me?
Mio is worried, too!
But good thing your leg grew back.
What's wrong?
The temple...!
Check for any more survivors.
What the heck...?
What's going on?
Who are you? Are you one of them too?
This girl came to do lewd business at our camp.
But we saw her enter the Sakai camp last night.
She's been disposed of for being a suspected spy.
Mio, Take!
Let go, idiot! How could you...!
I see you're one of them, too.
Who are you?
His arms...
Mio, wake up! Take!
Pick a red flower
Mio...
To give to her
Kill him!
What the...
You devil...!
No, Hyakkimaru...
You better hope the beast that comes out of the cave isn't a monster.
Spare me, please, I beg you...
Stop it, Hyakkimaru, stop!
Don't! You can't turn into a monster!
Please bro, come on!
Hyakkimaru, Mio had this with her.
It's seed rice.
She really got it back from the samurai.
To make her own rice paddy.
She didn't lose.
So you can't lose either.
Please...
Mi... o...
Here.
Pick a red flower
To give to her
In her hair
I will put the flower
Sorrow scatters in the wind,
piling up to form shadows
Our footsteps admonish indifference in such verbose ways
As I peek into your fathomless eyes, I lose my composure
Is there any hope in the place I am heading to?
I feign amusement and laugh
because this road is so dark
I will be there to shine the light
I'm used to playing at saying goodbye,
but I cried when I waved to you
Our fiery woes fade... and fade... until night falls upon us
If I knew tomorrow would be so mundane,
I wouldn't have said that I wanted to live
I know it's futile but can't help dreaming of a future... a future... you are to blame
"Arijigoku"