Wars had ravaged the land for years.
The soil was soaked with blood.
The wailings of the bloody survivors   could be heard throughout the land.
Just kill me, now!
Let those who live to rebel take this as a warning.
No dear, no!
Hang that up there too.
Party is over
But I still wanna dance
I can't even sleep
Someday, one day my passion's fire will
From the beginning I knew
One day the flames would die out
Hey, I thought I didn't need anything
But even now, I'm so serious
Ah... I still have time to make it
Ah... but I'm gonna burn it up, baby
Sorry darling, it's not that easy
But surely it's not that bad either
Give me fire
Light it up, baby. I'm gonna burn it up, yeah
Party is over
Sorry darling Hurry up Ah... I still have time to make it
Give me fire
Light it up, baby.   I'm gonna burn it up, yeah
#3 The story of Jukai
Hey, Kaname.
Hello.
This is for Doc.
Thank you!
It's nothing compared to what he did for us.
Thanks to him, my son can run around again.
This world isn't such a bad place with a man like him around.
Damn right.
You can move it with your shoulder muscles.
All you'll need is a little practice.
I have an arm!
I'm so happy for you, dear.
You're really letting me have this for free?
I do this because I wish to.
Thank you so much.
Master.
Teach this man how to use his new limb.
Yes!
Next.
Dr. Jukai is like Buddha himself.
Yes, he really is.
Master gave me a reason to live   when I was an orphan.
I'm so happy to be able to work here.
He's been up all night?
It hurts, Mama...
We're almost at the doctor's place. Hang in there.
It hurts!
What's the matter?
Is Dr. Jukai's home close by?
A passing samurai picked a fight with him and cut his arm off.
My poor son...
Don't worry. Master will save him.
It may take some time.
But I'll do everything I can.
Oh doctor, thank you so much.
I'm so relieved, did you hear that?
Yes...
I couldn't thank you enough.
He'll be running around again in no time.
I was afraid the doctor might be a scary man.
But I'm ever so glad I came.
You should never believe rumors.
Rumors?
N-Nothing...
Kaname?
Master.
Is it true?
That you used to serve Lord Shiba?
A foreign ship picked me up after I'd fallen into the sea.
I went with them to their country.
There, I learned how to make prosthetics for those who've lost their limbs.
I dare not say it's to atone for my sins.
But to just die peacefully as if nothing happened...
I didn't think it could be forgiven.
I was supposed to have died, but was made to live.
It meant there was something I still had to do.
During the war with the Shiba clan...
my father was killed.
Father, Father...!
Father!
You... You killed Father!
Kaname.
Please.
Begging for your life after what you did?
I care not for my life.
Do whatever you wish when this job is over. Just...
let me fulfill my promise to that child.
This is for him.
Thank you.
Thank you, Doc!
Farewell!
You could never atone for what you did.
You will never be my salvation.
It can't be... alive?
You wish to live?
"ONE YEAR LATER"
Is it born?
Yes, it is a boy, my lord.
You did it, my lady.
He will be my heir.
"6 YEARS LATER"
Seems like that crab took a liking to you.
Be careful, you'll scratch your mask up.
Here.
Let's take some home for dinner.
Time to head back.
Once again, I was made to live.
This boy is missing many body parts   and doesn't seem to hear me.
But, he has a curious power.
The strong power to survive.
"MARU"
This is your name.
"HYAKKIMARU"
There are things in this world more terrifying than a hundred demons.
But don't succumb to them, Hyakkimaru.
You will overcome them.
Hyakkimaru, are you okay?
Just what was that?
What is it?
Monsters.
They must be drawn to his powers.
Hyakkimaru.
I can't protect you forever.
In order for you to survive on your own...
You must be strong.
You win, sir.
Sir Tahomaru, how strong you are!
Yeah, I'm the strongest in this land!
Tahomaru.
Sword practice?
Father!
Oh, put me down.
Mother!
What is it?
Father, tell me about your last war.
Oh, all right.
I must dress his wounds.
He feels no pain, therefore he knows no fear.
He has no hesitation towards slashing and killing.
I only wished for one thing.
For him to overcome his destiny.
And live strongly.
That was all, at first...
Have I made the wrong decision again?
Hyakkimaru, are you okay?
What's the matter?
Hyakkimaru.
Your right leg.
You must've been rough on it.
Are you okay?
What the...
What's going on?
Impossible.
A leg. A real leg is growing.
How can this be?
Ghouls don't just eat people.
At times, they delude humans   and lend them their powers.
They let a person benefit   from their supernatural powers.
But in return, they take something away.
It may be that your body was taken   from you in such an arrangement.
I can't go with you. I'd only be in your way.
I couldn't do anything for you.
All I did was teach you to kill.
You had this with you when I found you.
It may help you one day to find your real parents.
So if he goes around killing monsters, he'll get his body back?
Yes, I suppose that's what it is.
Somebody must've made a deal with the demons a long time ago.
In return for that boy's body.
That's awful!
I don't know what they got, but his eyes, nose, mouth...
they gave it all away!
One must be prepared to go to hell to do such a thing.
What do these monsters want them for?
A single eye couldn't make their tummies full.
Who knows? Maybe it fulfills their souls.
What's that mean?
Hyakkimaru, you're up.
Huh? Hey.
It's hot, huh?
You've regained your sense of pain.
Stop it, you'll get burnt!
Geez, what do you think you're doing?
You dummy.
I cannot go anywhere.
Hyakkimaru.
Sorrow scatters in the wind,
piling up to form shadows
Our footsteps admonish indifference in such verbose ways
As I peek into your fathomless eyes, I lose my composure
Is there any hope in the place I am heading to?
I feign amusement and laugh
because this road is so dark
I will be there to shine the light
I'm used to playing at saying goodbye,
but I cried when I waved to you
Our fiery woes fade... and fade... until night falls upon us
If I knew tomorrow would be so mundane,
I wouldn't have said that I wanted to live
I know it's futile but can't help dreaming of a future... a future... you are to blame
"Kamaitachi"